Published using Google Docs

AIR MATH Privacy Policy

Updated automatically every 5 minutes

AIR MATH - PRIVACY POLICY HIGHLIGHT

Effective Date:January 21, 2022

Riiid, Inc. (“Riiid”) is incorporated in the Republic of Korea, having its registered office at  \[10F, Parnas Tower, 521, Teheran-ro, Gangnam-gu, Seoul. Riiid respects your concerns about privacy and is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to  websites, mobile applications(“App”) and AIR MATH services(“Service”) provided by Riiid.

OVERVIEW OF PRIVACY POLICY

In this Privacy Policy, Riiid describes the types of personal information Riiid processes through the Service, how Riiid may use personal information, how long Riiid may keep personal information, with whom Riiid may share it and the choices available to you regarding use of personal information and exercising your rights, including a right to object to some of the processing which Riiid carry out. More information about your rights, and how to exercise them, is set out in the “Your Rights'' section. Riiid also tells you how to contact Riiid about Riiid’s privacy practices. Below you will find a summary of the key topics contained in Privacy Policy. For more detailed information on how Riiid processes your personal information, please continue to read below.

AIR MATH - PRIVACY POLICY

1\. Information Riiid Collect

The categories of Information Riiid collects are as follows

Information You Provide Directly

* Account registration: When you create a user account, Riiid collects User ID, email address, grade information.
* Communication with Riiid: Riiid collects email address in order to respond to your requests, complaints and take appropriate actions.
* Surveys: If you choose to participate in a survey, you may be asked to provide certain information which may include personal information.

Information About Your Use of the Service

* Contents information: Your photos, search history, inquiry history, share history, and satisfaction Assessment.
* Device information: Your hardware model, current software version, IP address, operating system versions, and settings of the devices you use to access the Service.
* Log information: Diagnostic, technical, error, and usage information, including time and duration of your use of Service collected through cookies, pixels, tags, and similar tracking technologies that create and maintain unique identifiers
* Communications data : The Service may allow Members to engage in one-on-one communication using text chat. Riiid’s server may record and Riiid may retain records of the content of communications.

2\. How We Use the Information We Collect

Member registration and management

* Process Identification, verification of Member
* Prevent unauthorized use by third party
* Notification, announcement to Member

Service management and improvement

* Prevent illegal usage of Service
* Monitor, secure stability of Service
* Improve Service and develop new Service

Customer service

* Respond to your inquiries, complaints and take appropriate actions

Marketing and advertising

* Provide marketing services
* Suggest events, promotion

Statistics and analysis

* Analysis on Service usage information

3\. Information Sharing

Riiid shall share your personal information as below.  

AppsFlyer: Riiid provides User ID, User’s online activities on website and App to AppsFlyer to analyze, evaluate and improve Service and to diagnose any technical issues.

Riiid shall not share, provide, sell, or dispose of personal information to third parties without your consent. Nonetheless, Riiid shall provide your personal information to third parties on following events.

* Where special provisions exist in other laws or it is inevitable to comply legal obligations;
* Where it is inevitable for a public institution’s performance of its duties under its jurisdiction as prescribed by statutes, etc.;
* Where it is deemed manifestly necessary for the protection of life, bodily or property interests of yours or third party from imminent danger where you or your legal representative is not in a position to express intention, or prior consent cannot be obtained owing to unknown addresses, etc.

Pursuant to relevant laws, regulations Riiid may use personal information beyond the scope of purposes or provide personal information to third parties.

* Where information itself does not identify a particular individual and is necessary for academic research, statistics
* Where it is necessary for the investigation of a crime, indictment and prosecution;
* Where it is necessary for a court to proceed with trial-related duties;

4\. Retention of Personal Information

We take appropriate steps to ensure that we process and retain information about you based on the following principle:

* at least for the duration for which the information is used to provide you with the Service;
* as required under applicable law, a contract, or with regard to our statutory obligations (e.g., tax laws); or
* only for as long as is necessary to achieve the purpose for which it was collected, is processed, or even longer if required under any contract, by applicable law, or, in anonymized form, for statistical purposes, subject to appropriate safeguards.

5\. Your Choice

Riiid offers you certain choices in connection with the personal information we obtain about you. To limit communications you receive from us, or to submit a request, please contact us as specified in the Contact section. You may be able to opt-in to receiving push notifications from Riiid. We will send you push notifications if you agree to receive them regarding updates on the Services and other items that may be relevant to you.

6\. Your Rights

You may at any time, exercise the following rights to protect your personal information.

* Request to disclose your personal information
* Request for correction on errors in your personal information
* Request to delete your personal information
* Request to stop using your personal information

You may exercise rights by sending documents, phone calls, email, facsimile transmission (FAX), etc., and Riiid shall take appropriate action immediately. In the event you request correction or deletion of personal information, until such correction, deletion is completed, Riiid shall not use, nor provide your personal information.

7\. How we Protect Personal Information

We take protection of your information seriously and maintain safeguards designed to protect the information we collect in connection with the Services. However, please note that although we take reasonable steps to protect your information, no website, Internet transmission, computer system, or wireless connection is completely secure.

8\. International Transfer of Information

Your use of Service will involve the transfer, storage, and processing of your personal information within and outside of your country of residence, consistent with this Privacy Policy. In particular, your personal information will be transferred to the Republic of Korea.

9\. Updates to Our Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy may be updated to reflect changes in our personal information practices with respect to the Service, or changes in the applicable law. We will post a notice or send notification on our Service to notify you in advance of material changes to our Privacy Policy.

10\. Contact Us

For more information about our privacy practices, or to exercise any rights you may have pursuant to applicable law, please contact us at below address.

* Email address: help@airmath.com
* Address: 10F, Parnas Tower, 521, Teheran-ro, Gangnam-gu, Seoul, Republic of Korea
